# CHINONSO JOHN NKPOLUKWU

### **Web Developer Professional**

Address: 3012/220 Spencer Street, Melbourne, VIC 3000

Phone: 0401823031

Email: john.nkp1@gmail.com

Portfolio: johnnsonkp GitHub: https://github.com/johnnsonkp. Linkedin: chinonso-john-nkpolukwu

Software developer student and professional, with over 7 years of experience in customer service environments, seeking the successful application of software developer knowledge and customer service and IT experience into a Front-end Developer role.

#### **SKILLS**

Front-End Back End Source Control **FrameWorks** UI/UX Javascript ES6 / jQuery REST / MySQL Git(Git Flow) Bootstrap Wire-framing CSS / SASS/ SCSS MongoDB SCRUM / Agile Ruby on Rails Prototyping HTML Github **UML** 

## **PROJECTS**

Items: https://itemsv3.herokuapp.com

[ HTML // CSS/SCSS // Javascript // Ruby on Rails ]

→ A wish list shopping cart application designed to organise your online shopping items

NBA Stats: Inba-stats

[ HTML // CSS // Javascript ]

→ Web based application showcasing various NBA team and individual statistics.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Data Entry Officer, {REMOTE}
My Emergency Dr, Sydney - [2019 - Present]

- →Exceptional data entry for industry leader in tele-health
- → Providing administrative support to emergency medicine specialists and management team
- →Liaising with other allied health care professionals remotely

#### Member Care Consultant HCF Insurance, Parramatta - [2018 - 2019]

- →In depth understanding of the Australian healthcare system, and the ability to relay information to members.
- →Expert troubleshooting when handling members online queries.
- → Selling life insurance by educating members in order to meet daily and monthly KPIs.

# Customer Service Representative, Inbound & Outbound Specialist NRMA Motoring & Services, Sydney Olympic Park - [2016 - 2018]

- →Expert customer servicing, whilst identifying new sales, up-selling and cross-selling opportunities.
- →Cross-skilled in multitude areas including insurance, roadside assistance, inbound and outbound.
- →Fluency navigating range of business systems.

#### **EDUCATION**

- → Coder Academy / Full stack web developer bootcamp
- →RMIT / Bachelor of Information Technology

